const STORE = {
  rightAnswers: 0,
  questionBlocks: [
    {
      number: 1,
      question: `What does SVG stand for?`,
      answer1: `Scalable Vector Graphics`,
      answer2: `Simple Visible Greyscale`,
      answer3: `Skookum Valley of Gazette`,
      answer4: `Sorted Visual Glyphs`,
      correctAnswer: 'answer1',
    },
    {
      number: 2,
      question: `What language defines an SVG?`,
      answer1: `Javascript`,
      answer2: `Markdown`,
      answer3: `XML Markup`,
      answer4: `Rotokas`,
      correctAnswer: `answer3`,
    },
    {
      number: 3,
      question: `Which of the following statements is NOT true?`,
      answer1: `SVG images can render vector-style images a lot smaller than other formats`,
      answer2: `designers dislike using SVG images because they don't allow them to create multi-color icons `,
      answer3: `SVG is easy to animate`,
      answer4: `SVG provides some image editing effects, like masking and clipping, applying filters`,
      correctAnswer: `answer2`,
    },
    {
      number: 4,
      question: `What elements in an SVG can be animated?`,
      answer1: `only circle and rectangle`,
      answer2: `only line and path `,
      answer3: `only Rick and Morty`,
      answer4: `all elements can be animated`,
      correctAnswer: `answer4`,
    },
    {
      number: 5,
      question: `What do the cx and cy attributes define in an SVG circle element?`,
      answer1: `the circumference and diameter`,
      answer2: `the radius and the diameter`,
      answer3: `the center coordinates`,
      answer4: `the opposite to the C3 and P0 coordinates`,
      correctAnswer: `answer3`,
    },
    {
      number: 6,
      question: `What do the x1 and y1 attributes define in an SVG line element?`,
      answer1: `the end points for the x and y coordinates`,
      answer2: `the start points for the x and y coordinates`,
      answer3: `mimic the x2 and y2 chromosomes in healthy babies`,
      answer4: `the width of a line`,
      correctAnswer: `answer2`,
    },
    {
      number: 7,
      question: `what is the textPath element?`,
      answer1: `Adds text along the shape of a path element`,
      answer2: `The communication path between a CSS file and an SVG`,
      answer3: `A special lane on a pedestrian sidewalk for texting and walking`,
      answer4: `Defines the curves of a font`,
      correctAnswer: `answer1`,
    },
    {
      number: 8,
      question: `What does the g element do?`,
      answer1: `creates a global variable`,
      answer2: `creates a line on the g axis`,
      answer3: `defines the noun variable in a common greeting to a fellow gangster`,
      answer4: `allows you to group multiple elements`,
      correctAnswer: `answer4`,
    },
    {
      number: 9,
      question: `What is the best way to load an SVG if you want the most control?`,
      answer1: `In an \`<img>\` tag`,
      answer2: `In a 12 gauge shotgun`,
      answer3: `Inline HTML`,
      answer4: `In a canvas element`,
      correctAnswer: `answer3`,
    },
    {
      number: 10,
      question: `If the SVG is inline HTML`,
      answer1: `You cannot use Javascript on it`,
      answer2: `You must wrap it in an <a> tag`,
      answer3: `It could be accused of butting by the element behind it`,
      answer4: `You can change any SVG attribute using JavaScript`,
      correctAnswer: `answer4`,
    },
  ],
};
